Welcome to the night, the car is laid out for show Star shine is alright, watch the secrets unfold
There's magic in her hands Whisper what the future holds
The rhythm, yeah, yeah, yeah, whoa
Hearts in the balance, every card an open door
Feel the romance in every arcane
To a place where minds awaken and stories come alive,
Psyche Awakens TV isn't just content.
It's a community of creators, thinkers, and dreamers.
Every conversation sparks something new.
Every story awakens possibility.
We explore the depths of human experience
through innovative storytelling.
Join us.
Let your psyche awaken to something extraordinary psyche awakens TV where every mind finds its voice
Pull my dick out. Yeah, can you even intervene? Keep an eye on him. It's a chat talk to the chat
You know what I'm gonna do. I'm gonna pull my dick out better not how fast can you like delete the clip or whatever win
While you're wanting to save the video
So I'm gonna talk about you delete none of your business
Okay, I can't I can't I can't leave this guy for a second
yet here we are well i'm just gonna wait and i'm gonna laugh about everything even if it's not
funny so just give me a minute oh yeah do you think it's working through
little zaza i've even been around jamie like
Pull my dick out. Yeah, can you intervene? Keep an eye on him. It's a chat
Splits like an oath on stone
Wind carries names the dark has grown footprints burn where doubt once lay
I lift the flame and cut away.
Whispers circle, hungry mouths,
let them choke on smoke and vows.
I am the torch of the mountain,
bright against the storm,
fire in the marrow,
truth in living form.
Shadows break and scatter
when I call them by their name.
Torch of the mountain I walk the ridge and flame.
Mask after mask falls off the night.
Echoes confess beneath the light.
Rope of rumor, thread of lies.
I pull it once and watch it die.
Silence holds the higher ground, hear the iron of my sound.
I am the torch of the mountain, bright against the storm, fire in the marrow, truth in living form.
Nothing in the valley can un-make what I became.
Torch of the mountain I crown the ridge with flame, let the night keep its stories, I'll keep the fire.
what's up psych can you hear me my man
can you hear me yes hello
Yeah, I could kind of hear you. I'm just outside. I'm in front of a hospital. It's University Hospital
Okay, have I ever met you before?
You've never met me before. I'm a streamer. I probably know a lot of people you do. Yasmina, I know. Do you know her?
Yeah, I've been there. I recognize the name definitely
I've been in your chat. I'm the guy that writes one two three all over Tim Horton's bathrooms
Okay, so you're Canadian?
Yeah, I'm fucking Canadian, eh?
Yeah, you're a Prairie Page fan, eh?
Pardon me?
Prairie Page?
No, Prairie Page.
Are you speaking French? I don't speak French, man. I hate that language.
Oh, you're from the Montreal area.
I say Monestitabarnac.
That's it.
Well, how'd you find my show? You're a good-looking guy, I have to say, go ahead. Oh, yeah, yeah
Unfortunately, I like vagina a lot
Well, it's not is it wasn't fortunate for me not for you. I guess well chat's trying to turn me gay
I think every day and they think I'm gay. Do you know who pay is?
Who pay? Yeah, P-E-Y-T-O-M, Payton or something?
May?
Bay, I don't know. I don't know. I probably know them
Everyone's comfortable. I know I was good. I watch Alex Myers too, but she she used to be racist towards Canadians
So I was I was a little ticked off about that
Canadians like but they're not a race
He said we don't even matter
Well, you're a different country and I mean, I don't know what she said about it, but it's like I'm sure she was anyway
I like her now because she liked she was nice to blackout Andy
Well, I like I was trying to be nice black out anybody's really hard to be nice to because he keeps prom bombing me
And then he says I'm like a weirdo and when black black out any is calling me a weirdo
What exactly?
There's a lot of shit in this community. I fucking went off on Victoria tonight on her panel because
Like the shit she's been doing I don't agree with like
It's it's fucked up and I don't I don't know like people say all psychs are weirdo this psychs are weirdo that but
I don't know what that's based on
No, nobody said anything up like it's just fucking I don't know you're saying people say you're a weirdo or
Somebody said once and yeah in my chat. They said all Sykes are weird on yes. Meena was like no, he's not I like them
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know what thick, it's like I've never harmed anybody, I've never harmed anybody, it's like, I don't understand, like, like, there's thick, I don't know what thick, it's like, I've never harmed anybody, I've never harmed anybody, it's like, I don't understand, like, like, there's thick, I don't know what thick, it's like, I've never harmed anybody, I've never harmed anybody, it's like, I don't understand, like, like, there's thick, I don't know what thick, it's like, I've never harmed anybody, I've never harmed anybody, I've never harmed anybody, it's like, I don't understand, like, like, there's thick, I don't know what thick, it's like, I've never harmed anybody, I've never harmed anybody, I've never harmed anybody, I've never harmed anybody, it's like, I don't understand
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I can only fuck the sprinkler systems just fucking came on me
London I'm gonna be walking through the campus of
Western pretty soon
University of Western Elden John's husband went there
Did you ever watch that Dragon's, the Dragon's, that's a Canadian shark joke?
You ever saw that?
It's a TV show.
I just saw it, nobody else was live.
I just wanted to hop on a panel because I didn't want to go live on my own channel.
I just wanted to go on a panel and talk to somebody.
Instead of screaming at people in my chat.
I really like you, Jude Ho. I want to share something about Canada Ho once again. I didn't play it at all.
Oh, I can be a complete piece of shit.
Yeah. But, uh...
If you look at my channel, I've made, like, some AI videos recently. I've got into the AI game.
Yeah.
I've clipped a couple people, um, Janny, he was, uh, I've done clips.
I do AI clips of AI clippers because they get to clip everybody else.
So I decided I'm going to make clips of the Janny frog and cue the robot thing.
You know what?
It's like, I don't like Janny because Janny...
Um, it was like starting rumors and like trying to say I was like hitting on Benny Blanco and all this kind of stuff and then
All people say I'm Benny Blanco's dad. Fuck
I don't know
No, I don't fucking know man. I fucked a lot of chicks. You never know like I've only fucked like probably
Seven girls and not pulled out in the States and like three of them were in Florida like maybe a couple in Tennessee
I think they might have been related to the Whitaker's
I'm not sure
Roseanne was filmed in Canada, I didn't know that. Sorry, I could barely hear you.
Not Roseanne, hold on. I'm showing you this, I'm showing you a clip about something. Hold on, let's see if I can have it.
C-B-H.
Here it is right here. There you go.
Okay, ready?
Whoa, what's that?
Next in the den, a picture from Cawortha Lakes, Ontario.
Oh, my parents have a cottage up by there.
We have the blueprint for success.
Hello, dragons.
My name is...
I made coke with that, lady.
And I'm from the Cawortha Lakes region.
I'm here today to offer you 50% of my company for $2 million.
All right.
Arlene is in.
I think she's on fucking glue.
The building.
But this is not just any castle. This castle is built with straw.
Oh, great idea.
Castle Moto is the largest straw-built structure in the world.
It will be Canada's first indoor motocross resort.
Indoor motocross.
It's a straw indoor motocart resort.
Motocross.
It's made out of straw.
It is, Kevin.
Why, Norma?
Why?
Why motocross?
No, why do you want to do this?
Um, well, six years ago.
racing competitively myself and my husband.
We're sitting track side,
major thunderstorm,
lightning the whole nine yards,
and I look down along track side
and I see hundreds of riders
sitting, waiting for Mother Nature
because we cannot ride when there's electrical storms.
Obviously we're seasonal, we can't ride in the winter.
And you said there must be a better way.
Yes, exactly.
How many people will this seat
Each there's eight
Suites and each suite will sleep ten people you sleep care week. Yes. This is a full resort
You stay for a week or I see you watch the race and you sleep
Oh, it's like a Disneyland for motocross. Oh made out of straw. Yes, but Norma doesn't straw burn
normally it would Kevin but
straw bale structures. There's over 200 straw bale homes in Ontario.
It's true. You can build a house out of straw. You certainly can.
What else can you do in the resort? This resort will have a full gym, an indoor pool,
A complete pro shop.
Bust a track.
Three tracks.
How big is this thing?
This castle is just a little bit smaller than the Roger Center.
The Roger Center is 11.5 acres.
Oh my God.
The interior courtyard.
Does anybody have an idea what the Roger Center cost?
It's not built with straw.
That was their mistake.
No kidding.
Do you own the land I do so what's the land worth the partial that I'll be using for the castle is 200 acres
So the value is just under $200,000 for the 200 acres
Okay, that's land that has value. Yes, how much does it cost to build?
I know this castle is going to take almost 10,000 bales and it will be
Just a little bit over fifty thousand dollars for those bills. It's gonna cost you fifty thousand dollars to build it
But it's worth four million dollars
No, the total build will cost one point seven million. Yeah
Plus the land of two hundred is one point nine
Right, and I've upped it a hair because a couple mill. Yes, you call that a hair
Yeah, it's a routing error basically. It is normal. So let's think about this
There is a small chance that it may be worthless after you build it
You're kidding. I can understand your apprehensiveness
It is no it is a one or mind. I understand that this is a bad idea
Can you wait one minute? Yeah
I appreciate it Norma there might be three big bad wolves up here that are gonna
Huff and puff and blow your straw house down. I just am trying to give you some
morning I'm gonna be out now good luck may God be with you
So Norma look, why wouldn't I simply go rent an arena throw some mud in it like everybody else does in the motocross business?
Sell some tickets invite people to compete and have a motocross. Why do I want to build a straw castle?
Because our Canadian motocross industry is
Suffering from our season like I care. How do I make money?
Just the rentals of the units alone will make $1.5 million and I haven't even...
No, we won't.
Yes, it's $2,500 for a week.
Norma, sometimes the forces of evil can't be contained in hell
when a particularly bad idea comes up and it surges to the earth
and here it is now in Dragonstone.
I'm curious on why you think it's a bad idea.
Norma, put your earplugs in, it's about to come, okay?
Well before it does I'm gonna I'm like I'm a digital guy, you know you just want to escape and I'm allergic to straw
Pretty the top just long the whole tops long and I put it how long how long did I take Peter throw that grow that shit out like that?
It took like it took like a couple like great like a couple years or three. Yeah, bro
That's what I'm saying. We're like real talk man. I mean I am not trolling you it takes a while
It takes a while to grow that shit out. Yeah
Yeah, it took like about four four years. I think for that to happen
Holy shit, dude, I went from two to four years damn
I did grow my hair out one time, well, twice.
I ain't gonna lie, but I grew everything out.
The top, sides, back, everything.
And the first time it was like a year and a half,
and then I cut it.
And then the second time around,
it was like almost like two years,
but my shit was long though, you know?
Yeah.
And then I said, just fucking just buzzing it.
But shorter than this, this isn't buzzed, you know?
But yeah, I just buzzed, that's just.
Yeah, I just put in the pony the reason I put in the pony toes because that way, you know won't be in my face and stuff like that
It keeps it on my face
Well, that's how I had it to but I took care of my I took care of my hair when I had it fucking along
I mean, I would take me with good conditioner and shampoo and stuff. I got a lot of compliments. I mean, I'm not I'm not fucking around
about that but
The last time I grew my hair I was like over 10 years ago
That's the last yeah hit it long
Yeah, just like that bro. Just like that. Just like that. Yeah, it's just well
Yeah, it's the only part that's long goes the top like on the sides. It's like pretty like a short
Yeah, yeah, I mean I had everything thrown out though everything the sides top. I mean, yeah
Okay, I mean it was it was cool
I guess, you know, then I just fucking just buzzed all off after like almost two years. I just buzzed all off
Oh, so what made you get rid of it? Well, you said want to have any more you know what to be honest though
I mean it was just spontaneous. I grew it out, right?
And I kept it and then almost almost two years later. It was just spontaneous. I just fucking buzzed it
Yeah, you see you see how long it is in the back to see if I was yeah, bro. That's just long. Yeah, that's cool though. Yeah
But it's just been a ponytail though. That's why it's not all like down and stuff right now
So it's up in the ponytail
But it's from the back. This is all coming from the back
But I see some guys. I mean they have it like long on top and then they have it shaved off on the sides
They're like that's pretty cool. You know, yeah, that's kind of like what I'm trying to do
But it's like it's not a Mohawk though. It's more of like a longer. Oh
Okay, well that first time I grew my hair out, right and I was gonna cut it
and my brother's girlfriend was a hair stylist.
So we cut my hair down.
So it was like past my shoulders, right?
Everything, everything.
So she shaved it all down and she gave me a mohawk.
Yeah, it was so fucking cool.
Do you like mohawks though?
Well, I actually, I got to be honest with you.
That was the first time I ever had one,
but I thought it was like pretty cool.
You never had one before?
That's the only time you had one?
That yeah, and yeah, there is like native Native American, you know that runs through the family, but yeah, it was pretty cool though
I had no facial hair at the time by the way. I was 25. I do this
I mean, I chose, I mean, it's not, wait, wait, wait, it's still like I kind of grow out a mustache. I just had everything shaved
I didn't know what she was gonna do. She's like, let's give you a mohawk. I was like, let's fucking go
But that she was like standing up. I mean, it was standing up like like how do you do it? Like tall tall, you know, right?
Yeah, but we cut it down
But it was like from the front all the way to the back. No homo that she was fucking she did that shit nice, dude
I'm mad this fucking cut Ashley. What the fuck this I could go. I don't know who's in here, right? What'd be left? I
Think you got shy cuz I joined
So y'all know each other for pretty long or what I actually I don't even know the guy
I just found this channel just I just fell upon it. You can put an extreme yours on YouTube. I'm like, oh
Wow, who's life? Okay. Who's a psyche guy? That's literally how I found him. I never met him in my life
You'll never got that much familiar with each other. This is like the only couple times
I'll talk to what or not that much. I
Literally never met the guy in my life. This is the first time
I've been on his channel different times before. Oh, that's cool. That's cool. Yeah. Yeah, that happens on YouTube
I mean, no, I literally just stumbled upon his fucking channel. I said, let's fucking rock
You know, no homo kind of there and he's like, well, hey, I heard you talk about me. I'm like, I'm not the guy
I don't know what you talked about. I've never talked about your name. What are you talking about? I
Think he got me mixed up with somebody else didn't he got shine here anyway
Well, so he's not here anymore. Obviously, you know, he's literally left like 10 minutes ago
I've been meaning to talk to you about that. Literally. He's not here
Have you noticed?
That's what I was saying. Yeah, I
Was bringing that up. Yeah
Yeah, I don't know where he went
What the fuck
Right, isn't it weird that he would be in here, but all sudden he's not in here
Yeah, sucky this. I don't know
This
No, I don't do it. So do you do do you do anything like you play music or anything like that?
So I'm a drummer. That's why I had drummer in my name. Oh, that's cool as fuck. You know what now
I never gone to drums, but man, I respect the drummers man that
Because they're there that you gotta you gotta follow the rhythm in the drums, you know when you when people play in a band
That's cool. So I never
Go ahead, bro. I've been a drummer for I've been a drummer for a long time since I played drums
Hell yeah
How many years how many how many years they've been doing that I play since I was 11
But I'm in my 30s now. So about 20 something years. So you just do like like for your own like
Satisfaction or you like in a band or what?
I was supposed to be in a band
But I can't find people to play with because there's there's not many people that I can find around like that
I know and stuff that does that
Well, the great thing about the internet though is that you can find other people that will like like your style on vice versa, right?
And how do you find those kind of people?
You you're right on it right now. Well, this is through a third party, but on youtube youtube is a second
literally the second largest search engine in the world literally youtube
so
With that
Well, let me explain what you do is that you can put out some material if you want on your
own channel on YouTube, or you go and look, you know, and you like your style, like music,
right?
Yeah.
Seek out others on YouTube.
and when i know like always see if they're like across the world or across the country i make how the fuck you gonna do that but the thing is that you can do the drums and they consider that a stem.
That's a stem right there. I I was into music production before I know this is a stem, right?
so that's a stem right there and
They can get that stem that recording of you or vice versa that they can send something to you
And then you can play along with the guitar or or the bass or or the lyrics and that kind of thing
So it's either or but it's called stem. So, yeah
No, we're talking I'm not I'm not trying you. I'm being honest with you. Yeah, no, I'm not saying anything wrong
I don't understand anything wrong. I mean, well, I'm just saying that because you gotta you got to say you are in a trolling community
That sounds safe
Wait, why do people trolling here anyway, so like you're just trying to start like drama or I don't know
I mean, I'm so cool. You're so cool me who would hate us who would troll us who would cause that we're like so chill
Yeah, but you and I were just being like you and I were just being normal so I don't see why they're being like trolls like
I would never troll anyone in my life ever. I'm so cool. I've never said anything bad about anyone. I'm the same. Yeah, so
Who would come after me? Yeah, I mean, huh?
So would that be instead who would come after me, huh? I don't know. I mean, I don't think anybody like should
Well, they should it mister. I'm so cool as fuck. Yeah, I don't know
Anyways, I don't know where psyche said this is Larry. I just stumble upon his channel
He just said hi, you're cute and he is left. How did you find it though? Well, how'd you find the channel though like psyche's channel? I
Vaguely remember looking up rainbows
Who is that?
Just rainbows, you know like a rainbow I came across this channel. Yeah, it is it has popped up when he just typed that in like rainbows
And it's all sudden his channel popped up. No, I didn't pop up literally, but yeah, I popped up the channel
Yeah, that doesn't make sense if you're looking for rainbows. How would that pop up? I don't know
You don't understand that I
Can't make sense of it. No, you can't make sense of it. Yes, but I meant to say
I don't know. Yeah, I don't know. I don't know to tell you about that. I mean, I
Been me you talked to you about that. Yeah, like what's going on? Yeah. Yeah, I don't know
So what do you what are you doing are you are you smoking on something are you drinking something or what?
No, I just have a cold I think like my throat is sore and I think I'm kind of sick like something happened to me
You know what you want to fix this that a fucking tall can a tall can I
Think cough drops help right like you know sore cough drops. I like you know medicines
Well that too and made me drinking a tall can to wash those down. Yeah, what like gargle with salt water or something like that
Or what you gargle with some beer? Yeah, I mean you're talking. Yeah
Well, how's beer better than salt water that people say it's supposed to suck gargle with salt water when you have sword through
Well, the beer is there to take your mind off of what you're going through. Yeah, I mean, okay. Yeah
Telling people are having a hard time. You want to do some beers that takes your mind off all that shit
Like fuck all that bullshit. I just want to get drunk that kind of thing. You know, I mean, no, I can I can understand
It's just I don't really I don't really choose to drink beer that much. I don't ask me why I just something I don't really do it
I mean
Now I'm going to ask you why why I can't get used to the taste of it. I know it's weird, right?
I mean people like no
It's an acquired taste. Okay. How about
You drink wine
Maybe I
When I went to church as I drink wine but not like you know on my own like if I if I don't have it
I don't drink you drinking for Jesus. Yeah, that's
Yeah, one of my church
Baby Jesus, that's that's we're not talking about that. We're talking about getting
That's for communion, right? When you take yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, we're talking about getting fucked up and kind of wine shit. I mean like I don't know why I just I don't do it
I just what was okay. Okay. Hey, bro. No homo. What was the last time you got drunk? Let's just put like that. I
Don't think I've ever got drunk
reality
Wow
I'm not really much of a whole life. I've been alcohol-free drug-free like cigarette-free and stuff like that. Oh
That's good. So, you know, you almost like like straight edge. Yeah. Yeah, you can say that. Yeah
That there's nothing wrong with that. Hell, yeah, I never really just done it. I mean, so I
Mean, I mean it's just you have to have like you said you have to acquire taste, right?
So my taste when I drink something my taste comes from like sodas teas
Lemonade and stuff like that if I drink something
damn
Well, I mean if it works for you Matt just do it, I mean I mean it really matters what you want to drink right?
That's what I want to drink. That's why I stick with
Yeah, I I wrestled myself like an hour ago. I was like, okay, I have like one more drink here. I'm like
What do I want to do? I don't want to say it's really up to you like right like what you want to drink
Like it's really comes to like what you want like to drink
Yeah, yeah, so I
Was awesome panels earlier and just fucking around, right? Yeah
And so give like an hour break and then I had another drink right cracked it open
I'm like well, what do I want to do? I mean I literally thought about for an hour like literally real talk
Yeah, I was like do I want more alcohol or should I just chill with this?
But it took me an hour to think about that. So I just am just chilling. I never went back for more
What just pray a good thing?
Cuz I don't need I don't need any more alcohol. You know, I really don't I could have drank more about me fuck that
So what do you like to drink normally though just alcohol like I mean, that's your thing, right?
I mean may not be my thing, but is that your thing?
Yeah, just just beer just the cheapest shit I can buy
No, not the cheapest of them, I don't know just whatever
No, no, I've tried beer. Don't get me wrong. I've tried beer before but when I drink it
I was like, oh, I'm not used to this taste of this, you know
You have to be used to you know something when you drink it
That's, that's what Sam and said when someone tried to give him the hook and he goes, I'm
not used to this taste.
Yeah.
But they said, no, continue and you'll get used to it.
Well, well, if they make something else with it, you know, like the beer, like maybe put
like some kind of Coca Cola with it, I might be able to drink it a little bit more.
Well, that being said, you should be drinking like some like whiskey or rum with, with soda,
whatever.
Then that's different.
Yeah.
Yeah, so yeah, so you'll taste the soda with a little spice a little hint of whatever depends on how strong whoever makes it
That would be that would be more of an idea
I would think because that's what I'm more used to you know like that kind of stuff like soda more
I'm just saying double watch it because that shit can creep on you. Yeah
What is the psyche?
Hosty guy. Yeah, who was this guy? He just took off
I hear what you're saying, but I'm saying like why would you say it would creep up on you?
Is he trying to be like a matchmaker here? What the fuck psyche? No, dude. What the fuck?
He left you with he left us by ourselves like yeah, he did he thought he thought we're gonna hit it off
Can you call psyche real quick things call him come on his phone call? Who are you talking about somebody else?
I'm talking about the host of the channel. Can you call him real quick calm? Who me though? Are you asked? Yeah?
I'm I'm asking you to call Psyche the host of the channel. Just calm real quick. Just say hey, buddy
You know what? Oh
fuck
Jesus Christ
Wow, I don't know man
So what are you gonna do? Are you checking to stay here for that much longer?
Well, I mean he might be here right now or he might be here in two months. I don't know
You probably want to just leave because he's not here. No
No, I mean, I mean, I like I like the conversation. No homo. I mean, it's cool
Yeah, I'm not gay. No, I'm not gay either like I'm a straight guy
Yeah, I'm a sucker I do. Yeah, I know you're not gay
But I mean, no, but I mean, there's no words. There's time where psyche would want it, you know be gave with me
I was like, I'm not really like really
Yes, like he really told me that before he says he's like I'm a guy that he would want it
You know kiss and stuff like that and date. I was like, I don't really do that kind of stuff though
Shit really I'm being serious. No, no
Okay, okay. Wait, okay. Let's talk about this. No was this on panel or is this backstage?
No, this is actually on here like how we're on here right now, you know talking on the you know live stuff the live stream
really
I'm not
It's not it's not the wrong. He just expressed that he liked you. Yeah. Yeah, but I told him I'm not gay though
I don't I don't go back. I like guys. I mean I like guys as friends, but I don't date guys though. I'm like, yeah
But, okay, so he expressed that, hey, you're hot, you know, you are, you know, cream of
the crop kind of thing.
So when you told him that, hey, I don't pop from the rough, I'm not, you know, gay for
pay kind of thing.
But did he still pursue after that?
Yeah, he was still coming at me different times, like different days or different times
This fucking guy
Man, this is no this not like I'm making this up or anything like that if you ask him
He'll probably tell you like all this stuff that happened. Oh, no trust. No trust me. I believe you. I trust me. I believe you
Yeah, I believe you dude. I believe you wholeheartedly. I believe you
I know you would not make this up. Trust me. There is others that
No, psyche, but I mean he just likes you though. I mean you can't you can't blame the guy for liking men
No, I told him that I said I know I had the company and your friend, but I don't want to be anything else other than that
No, how okay?
Let's let's do a little
Deep dive. Can we do a deep dive real quick? How did you come across?
How can how okay? How did you come across psyche channel?
Or psyche well, we both appeared in his channel
So that question could be asked for both of us, but you said rainbows, but mine was a different way, right? Yeah
I just found him through somebody else's channel when I was on somebody's name
Be the that witch oh there she's she's the devil you guys stay away from her don't ever go to that channel
Heard about her she is the devil don't ever go there she will curse you
She never said anything wrong to me
Well, that's a whole thing though, you think everything's fine then you wonder why after that she's going wrong in your life
She will curse you she's the fucking devil
Well, she never did it yet though if she was gonna do that though to me, you know what I'm saying like she never started with that
Listen buddy, don't ever let Jigard down. Especially with men like that. She is a man by the way, okay?
You know that I thought she's a woman. She looks like a woman to me. Okay. What don't you don't say that?
That's that's wrong. We call pronouns. Okay
Wait, are you serious?
We call pronouns pronouns now. Okay. She's a pronoun he she pronoun. Yeah
What do you mean?
Have you ever seen that woman came up?
No
Yeah, it's a pronoun
I'm trying to understand what's going on like you say she's a man or what?
who knows we just called pronouns now that she's a pronoun pronoun yeah he he she it whatever he
she it is just weird i'm just confused i mean she never did you're confused i'm confused too
but do i want to go around that town show a curse you or he that pronoun will curse you don't do
And it should it should remain like that. Yeah
Huh, it should it should remain like that. Don't ever go back there. Don't ever go back. Okay
So since then have you been on psyches? Have you watched psyches? Does he talk about that pronoun? I mean, I don't know
No, he talks about beat any shows are in clips and stuff on this channel like he shows videos ever
Or you said pronoun. I know like he or she but yeah, yeah
He she the pronoun is weird really weird. Yeah, just saying
Wait, so psyche's not coming back you don't think um, I I don't know it's the first time I ever met him
Don't know right now, huh? He's he's probably talking to that pronoun right now to be honest
Okay
I'm the same. I think he is
Whoa, you like to drink beer like usually well, I did I did have some earlier, but now I'm just drinking this
Don't know what it is. Is that like a spike drink like a spike lemonade or something?
Yeah, somebody spiked this and I just started to drink it, you know
Yeah
Makes me feel kind of funny inside, you know
Does it have like a good flavor to it though? Like it's not just regular like beer. I mean the alcohol drink or something
It's
How can I say?
It's like doable. It's like casual. I guess it's it's not too heavy like beer. I guess
It's like a light
Alcoholous drink. Yeah. Yeah, exactly
Yeah
So, um, what else do you have that's all you have for right now like to drink? Um,
Well, I did have a lot before that
Okay a lot a lot a lot
But well, it's tiny like 10 minutes ago was like when I was contemplating before I joined the psyche channel, I mean
Should I just chill out and just drink this one or should I go back for more?
Go back for what though with more alcohol, but it took me a whole hour to think about that, right?
Yeah, you know, it's like well, I should just chill. Yeah with this
It's up to you man. You drink what you want to drink remember. I told you comes down to that earlier. Yeah
Hey, okay
I'm gonna ask you a question but no homo. Have you ever been like bi curious?
What does that mean?
that means that
You're not really like the bisexual or gay, but you like thought about it
Sometimes no, I mean there's times I had there's times I had it in my thoughts
But I never really wanted to do anything sexual, you know with another guy. I just know
Yeah, well there you go. You're you're curious about it. Yeah. Yeah
There's nothing wrong with that, you know, it's you're saying that
Who knows I mean, maybe you might meet a great guy, I mean
I'm trying to say it's okay to be friends with guys
But I mean when it comes to dating somebody that's be a woman because that's the way he's supposed to really be I think
That's why it's meant to say who said that who said that wait who said that
That's what God says. That's what it says in the Bible
Oh my gosh, so you think God is gonna judge you if you choose to be with a man think about that really I
Thought that's a natural way to get you know things done is to be with the opposite sex
Well, do you plan on having a family?
It depends. I mean, I don't know if I'm I don't think I'm ready right now, but in the future
I probably you know, I mean, I mean, I mean I'm just
Do you plan on having like kids?
If it happens, it happens. I mean, I don't know
Yeah
But also too with that being said there's maybe that that part of you or something in that
That you're just
You kind of you two guys there's nothing wrong with that, okay, wait, what's wrong? No, I'm saying there's nothing wrong
You're you might be into guys, you know, there's nothing wrong with that. Oh, it's friends. No, I mean, it's friends, but not nothing else though
Yeah, I mean even that me whatever is I mean, I got a lot of guy friends. I
Have a lot of guy friends. I
Mean cuz I thought most guys they really go for women just think about it if you ask a guy if they want a woman
They're probably say yes, right if you ask a guy if they want to be with a woman
True, true. But I'm going by what you have thought before. You have thought about men in a certain way.
I already gave you my opinion though. Like I said, it's okay to be friends with guys, but that's all I really see out of them.
Yeah, and there's nothing
Unless they're unless they're family like brothers, you know or something like that or uncles didn't they I see them as family
And that's it and you what I honestly just just do what works for you. I'm not trying
I'm not I'm not fucking around being honest. Just do what works for you what feels right to you. Okay?
I feel like that's a natural way for me. That's what I'm thinking. Yeah, I'm not judging
I know others would want to troll you and this and that and I'm not doing that. Okay
Yeah
Just do a worse for you. Okay. I'm not saying you're I'm not saying you're saying anything wrong
It's just I know you're just curious. You want to know what's what I think it's tough, right?
Yeah, I'm curious to an extent. I know I don't want to know too much
Yeah
But, uh, I am, yeah, I still am a little curious, but I mean, I don't want to know.
I don't want to know, like, details, anything.
Can you be honest with me, though?
Like, you're into women, though, right?
If you had somebody to be with.
Um, yeah, I love women.
That's what you go for, right?
Women?
Yeah, I love women, and women love me, oh, yeah.
You know to be honest so and just bright clip. Oh, which I don't care
Over the years. There's man that have hit on me, but I said, no, I'm straight simple as that
That's what I was trying to explain to you. It's just simple as that. You just got to tell him
I'm just not into guys. I mean, I don't mind being their friend is what you could tell them, right?
But they say don't go you don't have to go any further though than that
Well, what with that? I I was I wasn't their friend to be
And keep us strong enough
What made you know?
It was just a friend though. They were just men in public
They weren't getting along with you is that why he said they're not your friend
We were never friends it was just men in public
They'll just like acquaintances right that means y'all don't really
Not even that they're just men in public
Y'all just said hi to each other and that was it. I mean, that's what acquaintances do
That's not really defined as an acquaintance
It was a hi from there in oh fuck
What what's wrong?
What the fuck I
Can't believe you're talking about this. Yeah, I just
Okay, now now we're cheap to my name to Sam and okay, can you okay? Have you ever seen me in chat?
My name is Sam and NYC. Okay, that's me
You're not the one that's Alexander. That's somebody else, huh?
No, that's Andrews right there. You see you see him talking. I'm my name is Sam and NYC. Yeah, I
Never saw that one in the chat though. You said this your first time on this
Well, I'm gonna hook you real quick. I'm gonna hook you listen
I'm gonna be honest. I'm a little shy, but I love men. Oh my gosh. I love men. Oh my gosh. I love men
Yeah, I love him so much
I'm standing are you just joking about that? I mean like that you want to be with me
No, I'm being fucking honest
You told me earlier that you want to be woman. I I'm insured myself. I don't know a pronoun to use
But my name is Sam out. Okay. I'm
Gays gays can be
But I mean I like women too, but I love men I love hot dogs. I mean, it's really up to you man
I mean you decide what you want
Well, that's what they say you
Oh, fuck he dropped. Oh, well. And now I'm taking over operations.
I'm fucking Sam it. I'm fucking fag man. And we see. No, no, no, no.
I don't I'm not gonna say that. I'm sorry, psyche. I didn't I didn't mean like that.
Well, what are psyche yet? Well, I was the psyche.
You know as I'm not gonna do anything stupid. I'm like a problem
With that being said does anybody have any burning questions for me, I didn't plan on fucking joining no homo. I just
Does anybody have any questions for me? I don't know what's like is it wait wait hold on when I fucking join
What the fuck was he watching? What is that? Who's who taught him how to watch that kind of shit? That's so stupid
Just stop
Alexander what's up, bro? I'm Ria
Shit and John then what's up, bro? I've ever seen you around here. What's up? What's up?
Oh shit, what happened at home boy?
The riser by the way, let me raise you
Not only I'm gonna raise her but I'm a riser 2.0
So the first time wasn't good enough or the second time's gonna be even better. How was that work 2.0?
By the way, what is this?
What is this?
John then I don't know bro. He just like took off
We talked for literally like a few seconds and he just like dropped
Alexander what's up, bro? I haven't seen you in a while. Well, I mean I haven't been around this shit in a while. I
Do it man
Alexander always brings that fucking content
Know what happened Alexander. I mean Alexander. What the fuck are you know him fucking call him on a discord or whatever just say like hey, man
You got something on your stream right now. I mean, I don't know where you went
Bro you gotta fucking call him something like that
Or Alexander or whoever you gotta have like an admin here you gotta fucking join something
I mean I can I can run this shit on my own. I'm just saying I mean this is in my channel though
I mean I fucked what I don't I'm not okay
How do I say this I
Don't fuck with sake like that
But I mean I should troll him and fuck around with him
But I mean I don't have nothing against him so I should join his pounds. It was cool. I never poor bomb him
It was cool. I never say anything bad
But I just joined like right now, but I mean I don't know him like that though Alexander
That better make sense, fool.
I think I just made that clear.
Oh, fuck. Shit.
What? No. Really, Alexander?
Is that how it is? Bro, really?
What the fuck did I miss, Alexander? Really? That's how it is now?
Oh fuck, so how is it Alexander, when I should come through, I mean, I actually watch it, but if I happen to come across
Saki's channel, you still have people on this panel, right?
I already actually clicked on it, but I can see from the thumbnail, I'm like, oh shit, yes, the people, good for him
Yeah, I just fucking just whatever
That makes sense
I don't accept anyone so it comes across algorithms just through the thumbnail
So that's not happening anymore. I don't I don't know what's going on
Really, Johnathan?
Oh, fuck.
Beta is.
Beta's live right now?
Should I go over there and fucking destroy her?
I was there earlier.
Are you serious?
She's fucking live right now?
This bitch has no fucking life.
Serious.
Her fucking life is just me.
Are you, shut the fuck up.
She's literally live right now?
Oh my gosh.
This lady is fucking misbrow as fuck.
Holy f-
I'm gonna accept her!
I mean look- I mean look her up manually.
Are you fucking serious?
Look at-
Burn Witch at the stick.
Holy fuck, she's live right now. Are you fucking serious? Holy shit. Oh
My gosh
This chick has no fucking life. Oh
Does she do that see I'm not around like I used to does she really do that though?
She'll just go live like in random times or what?
Don't know. I'm just asking I
Did send her some messages though behind the scenes and she probably didn't like it which I don't give a fuck
I really don't care. I
Wish I really wish she would show those messages to you cuz I got nothing to hide. I was calling her fucking out
Was calling her out
I've had her person number since last year
And she has my person number, but yeah, I called her out earlier. She probably didn't like that. I don't give a fuck
I was speaking facts I can show that I can literally showed what I fucking sent her I got nothing to hide nothing
I called that bitch out and yeah, I said bitch I called that bitch out
She's a narcissist. What if I'd?
We're talk
If she doesn't like how I'm exposing her I mean how about just chill the fuck out stop doing that shit. How about that?
Simple was that
Now I
Don't have a channel anymore ideally did like
Whatever, I don't care about these channels. I can try to join hers or her panel
I don't think she'll let me go because I caught her out behind the scenes. I
Caught her out behind the scenes. I don't think she'll let me join. I
Know maybe she will
What's up, bro? What's up, D? What's up, bro?
How you doing, man? I
Don't know. Maybe should I try should I try to join your fucking panel? I
Know she'll let me I
Was seeing some but I speak in fact, so I'm not talking shit
Behind the scenes
Now, before today, when was the last time I ever messaged you behind the scenes?
Was July 4th?
Go talk.
If I join her panel, she goes, oh, well here's Carl. This is what he said to me
Behind the scenes. Yes, show all that shit and I stand on that. Yes. Yes. Yes. That's me
Yeah, that is me. I said that shit. Hell, yeah
And I stand on that shit
So I mean, what should I do? Should I fucking stay here and carry this shit?
I don't know we're psychies that or should I join her panel and fucking cause havoc. I don't know
I'm not trying to cause havoc. I just whatever
I just want you
But I'll press her though. I'll press her for her shit. I
You know why she went live. I don't know what the whole gig is. It's none of my business to be honest
Christ
Daryl a D bro a shy shy join this shit just to fuck around
Should I just I just do it just to fuck around with her or what should I?
Really
Guys when I come to your wife. She lets me up. Oh fuck. I'm gonna come through. I mean what if anybody saw earlier
I'll come through like I don't give a fuck dude
I like summer though, but summer is an activist so she wants to go out to anyone. I'm like chill the fuck
I like summer. I like some
but
We're not opposing your cause when you we're not
Opposing activists chill out so I mean I I respect what she's doing. I mean, that's awesome. Okay, what she's doing
But we're not
I don't know, I think I do.
All right, Alexander. Okay. Well, wait, Alexander. Do you still join her?
Bro, bro, bro. Wait, wait, wait, Alexander. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Alexander used to come with a heat.
Alexander, do you still join her panels or does she let you? I have been running a while. I haven't seen, you know,
I'm not always watching.
If you see me, well, I was streaming for a small time and I do leave that shit. But Alexander,
If you don't see me on panels, or I'm on this panel right now, or if you don't see me in chat typing away
I'm not there. I'm literally not there. So
Alexander you got it. Hey, bro, you got to catch me up to speed
Have you been on her panel? Are you boycotting? Does she have your blog? What's going on?
Because when you come through man, you come through like all cool that you just like turn that shit up dude
Dude, you guys have cool content
Really, I mean, I don't do shit like that, but Alexander don't give a fuck, dude.
You'll come through like a wrecking ball, dude.
Yeah.
What's up?
Oh, I tell you, okay.
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
Oh, really?
Okay.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Alexander.
Does she have you blocked?
Hey, bro, let's join together.
Have you fucking nuts?
Yeah.
she'd be like so overwhelmed you're like what the fuck is this like what is
this yeah let's go together this fucking let's just fuck that shit up we got a
great content cuz I'm not just boring that's why I was doing earlier well I
was trying to but she's like oh go do your own thing I don't have my own
thing I don't have a channel damn as well there's it
Let's hold hands. No homo. Shut the fuck up. Seriously, Alexander. I'm gonna go right now
Are you are you gonna join? I can join on my own. I mean if you want to watch or wherever
I'm not gonna hold your hand broke
Let's go
Okay, let's go
Okay. All right. Well, I'm gonna I don't wear a psyche set, but I'm gonna I'm gonna drop out of here
I'm gonna go in her shit